teacherph.com 2016-05-06

# Privacy Policy - TeacherPH

The Internet is an amazing tool. It has the power to change the way we live, and we’re starting to see that potential today. With only a few mouse-clicks, you can follow the news, look up facts, buy goods and services, and communicate with others from around the world. It’s important to TeacherPH to help our users and customers retain their privacy when they take advantage of all the Internet has to offer.

We believe your business is no one else’s. Your privacy is important to you…and to us. So we’ll protect the information you share with us. To protect your privacy, TeacherPH follows different principles in accordance with world-wide practices for customer privacy and data protection.

  * We won’t sell or give away your name, mail address, phone number, email address, credit card number or any other information to anyone.
  * We’ll use state-of-the-art security measures to protect your information from unauthorized users.

 **NOTICE**

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you create a Registration ID on the site or when you download documents, free software, enter a contest, order e-mail newsletters or join a limited-access premium site. We use your Personal Information for four primary purposes:

  * To make the site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.
  * To help you quickly find software, services or information.
  * To help us create content most relevant to you.
  * To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from TeacherPH.

 **CONSENT**

If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of TeacherPH.com. But you will not be able to access areas that require registration.

If you decide to register, you will be able to select the kinds of information you want to receive from us by subscribing to various services, like our electronic newsletters. If you do not want us to communicate with you about other offers regarding TeacherPH products, programs, events, or services by e-mail, you may select the option stating that you do not wish to receive marketing messages from TeacherPH.

 **ACCESS**

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time at the User Center. There, you can:

  * View and edit personal information you have already given us.
  * Tell us whether you want us to send you marketing information, or whether you want third parties to send you their offers by postal mail.
  * Sign up for electronic newsletters about our services and products.
  * Register. Once you register, you won’t need to do it again. Wherever you go on TeacherPH.com, your information stays with you.

 **SECURITY**

TeacherPH has taken strong measures to protect the security of your personal information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honored. We take strong precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

TeacherPH strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

Your personal information is never shared outside TeacherPH without your permission, except under conditions explained above. Inside TeacherPH, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. Your information may be stored and processed in United States or any other country where TeacherPH, its subsidiaries, affiliates or agents are located.

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your user name and password, so do not share these with others.

 **NOTICE TO PARENTS**

Parents or guardians: we want to help you guard your children’s privacy. We encourage you to talk to your children about safe and responsible use of their Personal Information while using the Internet.

The TeacherPH site does not publish content that is targeted to children.

 **ENFORCEMENT**

If for some reason you believe TeacherPH has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by e-mail at teacherph.com@gmail.com, and we will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly. Be certain the words Privacy Policy are in the Subject line.

 **CUSTOMER AND USER PROFILES**

As mentioned above, every registered user/customer has a unique personal profile. Each profile is assigned a unique personal identification number, which helps us ensure that only you can access your profile.

When you register, we create your profile, assign a personal identification number, then send this personal identification number back to your hard drive in the form of a cookie, which is a very small bit of code. This code is uniquely yours. It is your passport to seamless travel across TeacherPH.com, allowing you to download documents, free software, order free newsletters, and visit premium sites without having to fill out registration forms with information you’ve already provided. Even if you switch computers, you won’t have to re-register – just use your Registration ID to identify yourself.

 **LOG FILES**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as PLDT, Smart or Globe), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Google Chrome or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

 **COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on TeacherPH to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

 **DoubleClick DART cookies**

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”).

The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Lazada, you may see Lazada advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about Smartphones). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.

You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

 **COLLECTION & USE OF NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION**

TeacherPH automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. TeacherPH may use this information to customize the content you see and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services. However, TeacherPH does not connect this non-personal data to any personal information collected from you.

 **WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION YOU SHARE**

When you join us, you provide us with your contact information, including your name and email address. We use this information to send you updates about your order, questionnaires to measure your satisfaction with our service and announcements about new and exciting services that we offer. When you order from us, we ask for your credit card number and billing address. We use this information only to bill you for the product(s) you order at that time. For your convenience, we do save billing information in case you want to order from us again, but we don’t use this information again without your permission.

TeacherPH will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on TeacherPH or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of TeacherPH and its family of Web sites, and, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of TeacherPH, its Web sites, or the public.

 **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

TeacherPH may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. When it does, TeacherPH will also revise the “last update” date at the below of this Privacy Policy. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of the SITE after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.

 **QUESTIONS OR SUGGESTIONS**

If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please [contact us](http://www.teacherph.com/contact-us/) directly.

 **Last update:**  January 16, 2016
